Do y'all remember this story from last year? Please watch.
Here's an update on a hero who saved this man's life a year ago. She heard the man, that's him
right there, screaming for help in Buffalo, New York during the blizzard at Christmastime 2022.
So she took him in and fed him. She covered his frostbitten hands. She tried to warm them,
but only after she cut the bag off of his hands, the bag he was holding for hours in the snow,
screaming for help, had become one with his skin. She used those garden shears to cut a ring off of
his finger. She bathed him. She took him to the bathroom. She cooked meals that he specifically
asked for, and she played the Buffalo Bills, which he requested. He is Joey, a mentally disabled man
who has the mentality of a child. He was on his way to work during the blizzard when he got stuck in
the storm and was dying in the snow. She is Shakira, the woman who saved his life. And here's how she
has been rewarded. The governor of New York honored her as a good neighbor. Her kids, along with her
partner, Trent, who helped her to save Joey's life, were sent on a free Disney vacation. JetBlue flew
them there. The NFL sent them to the Super Bowl, which Trent loved. And Shakira was like, okay, sure,
I'll do that. And Shakira bought a home. It was her dream. Nearly $200,000 was donated to her by
strangers who were touched by what she did and wanted to help her. And as for Joey, he and Shakira
see each other all the time. They're very close. He lost all of his fingers. They're hoping to get
him prosthetics this year. I don't know if y'all remember this story, but we had the honor of having
Shakira on Small Doses Podcast, where she told us the story in her own words. Check it out,
side effects of being a good Samaritan. I am so happy to see that so many blessings have been
bestowed upon her for her simply showing up in the kindness that she would just do
any day because that's just who she is. Congrats, Shakira!